the future of working is remote but the
future of management is remote
controlled I'm Doug Yen and I'm bringing
the remote control to remote working in
2020 I had to Pivot my managerial style
to work on Zoom so when I asked all my
employees to come back to the office I
had a problem how could I be there for
them without actually being there for
them thanks to 3D printing and a little
duct tape I had a solution everybody
knows you don't want to micromanage but
a physical presence is important for
office morale now I can get back to
collaborating with my team mingling
around the office and most importantly
team
building I can feel the Synergy
again there is some maintenance involved
but internal feedback has been very
positive happy birthday birthday to me I
know thank you all right H you can only
be 35 so many years am I
right I've also been experimenting with
different Mobility options sometimes you
want to feel like you're just strolling
around the office like normal there are
some Kings to work out but hey it's not
like Steve Jobs built the iPod in a day
you got to keep people on their toes you
never want your management style to get
too predictable though there's been a
handful of HR concerns good management
requires subtlety while I love to feel
like I'm in the trenches with my team
nobody wants to feel like somebody's
hovering over their shoulder so I hover
10 ft above their head what are you
saying
the the expense report for September do
you know you have
I've been known as a disruptor in the
industry for business travel it helps to
have more compact Solutions people
respect someone willing to show up as a
children's doll and hey it's not all
work and no play around here I still get
to let loose on wacky Wednesdays things
have been going so well I've allowed
some folks to work remotely again sure
there's been some internal feedback
calling my management style a creepy
over engineered excuse but like open
Office layouts and unlimited vacation
days some workplace revolutions just
take a little getting used
to oh my oh
my fine some folks just can't think
outside the box I'm fine
Chris you
[Music]